Finding Aid for Washtenaw County Dental Society Women’s Auxiliary records, 1946-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Washtenaw County Dental Society Women’s Auxiliary records 1946-1982
Washtenaw County Dental Society. Women’s Auxiliary.
3 linear feet
85484 Bf 2
President's books containing minutes, reports, and other organizational material.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were deposited by the organization (donor no. 6203 )
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The women's auxiliary of the Washtenaw County Dental Society was established in 1946.
The record group includes president's books containing minutes, reports, and other organizational material. There are also minute books, 1946-1974, membership directories, and scrapbooks of activities.
Subjects:
Dentistry--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Women--Michigan--Washtenaw County--Societies and clubs.
- President's book
  - 1956-1959 (Box 1)
  - 1959-1965 (Box 1)
  - 1965-1968 (Box 1)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Minutes
  - 1946-1954 (Box 3)
  - 1954-1962 (Box 3)
  - 1962-1968 (Box 3)
  - 1968-1974 (Box 3)
- Other records
  - Directories, 1947/1948-1975/1976 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks, 1965-1979, 3 volumes (Box 3)
  - Committee Reports, 2 folders (Box 3)